<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Kamesh.xyz</title>
    <link>https://kamesh.xyz/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Kamesh.xyz</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kamesh.xyz/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Being Born Poor is Not Your Fault But Dying Poor is</title>
      <link>https://kamesh.xyz/posts/born-poor-not-your-fault-but-dying-is/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kamesh.xyz/posts/born-poor-not-your-fault-but-dying-is/</guid>
      <description>I strongly belive education has nothing to do with being rich, anyone could become richer or rise above poverty level if they have tirst and the ability to compare, Investigate and taking initiative.
Today let&amp;rsquo;s say you are earning 100 rupees per day and a person you know is earning 200 rupees per day, try to figure out what he is doing to get that extra 100 than yours and try to apply the same, it&amp;rsquo;s a try and won&amp;rsquo;t going to cost you much.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating User-Centric Products: A Guide to Achieving Success in Product Development and Marketing</title>
      <link>https://kamesh.xyz/posts/user-centric-products/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kamesh.xyz/posts/user-centric-products/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m obsessed with developing products which are super easy to use without compromising the ability to achive what&amp;rsquo;s exactly needed for the end user.
Today anyone could build a product, but the ability to market and sell maters, and it should be naturaly communicated by product itself is what I belive.
Below is my view on criterias to achive them,
Know why you are building, for whom you are building and what you are building</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Pitfalls of Blindly Following Hierarchy Trends in Startups</title>
      <link>https://kamesh.xyz/posts/pitfalls-of-hierarchy-in-startup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kamesh.xyz/posts/pitfalls-of-hierarchy-in-startup/</guid>
      <description>Today I could see many startups adding fancy hierarchies to their system.
Adding layers of unnecessary hierarchy due to the hype just others doing it will ruin the business rather than benefiting in the longer run.
The more you add the layers of hierarchy, the complex the business is to operate, slowers the phase which the company used to operate and most importantly will change the mindset of people from owning the work to being worked.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting an Adventure: Exploring Startups, Coding, and More</title>
      <link>https://kamesh.xyz/posts/adventure-begins/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kamesh.xyz/posts/adventure-begins/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m Kamesh Sethupathi, and I&amp;rsquo;m super excited to welcome you to my own website. I&amp;rsquo;ve been a frontend developer for 5 years, and I&amp;rsquo;ve worked with cool companies like Zoho and TestSigma. My journey in tech has been fascinating, and I&amp;rsquo;m eager to share what I&amp;rsquo;ve learned with you.
On this site, I&amp;rsquo;ll talk about various stuff, like coding, making cool things, and the world of startups and businesses. I want to show you what&amp;rsquo;s up in the tech world and maybe inspire you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
